Soon, very soon...
Ultimate
The world will belong to Gekko!
Episode 12    Eternal Rivals
Delicious!
They're like little hamburgers!
They're macarons.
And I made lots, so there are plenty
more where that came from.
Thanks.
Oh, and Desumi-san.
It looks like I'm going to
be in another commercial.
Here's the outline.
I can't wait!
What's it for this time?
It's some bridal thing.
Twitch
What? It's just my usual commercial stuff.
Kishimoto Weddings, Ltd
New Commercial
Our Wedding Is On
Outline
"Our Wedding Is On"?!
Our Wedding Is On
Outline
And his costar is...
"Bride"
Anna Hashimoto
The current big star, Hashi-An?!
The Cutest  Anna Hashimoto
In-Depth Guest
Beshakuri
The one who just said that Red's
her favorite member of Gelato 5...
What is it, Desumi-san?
"Scene 1. The couple enters the chapel."
Desumi-san?
"Scene 2. They gaze at each
other before the priest."
Hello, Desumi-san?
"Scene 3. They cut the cake."
D-Desumi-san?
Then the line: "For your big
day, choose Kishimoto Weddings."
Desumi-san?
Fudo-kun...
Y-Yes?
This is one job that you dare not accept.
Wh-Why not?!
But I have to, Desumi-san!
The rest of the team turned them down!
My fans would be distraught to
see me in a commercial like that!
I'll pass, thanks.
It's incompatible with my image.
So I'm the only one left!
Well, you can't do it, either!
What's wrong with you, Desumi-san?
You've never been this selfish before.
Selfish?
This is my job.
How can I—
Fine, then!
Go cut your cake with Hashi-An or whatever!
Wait, Desumi-san!
Desumi-san!
What in the world happened there?
I heard everything!
Haru-kun?
It's not nice to eavesdrop!
But yes, please tell me...
Why is Desumi-san so upset?
It's just a commercial!
"Just a commercial..."
Yet it is a commercial.
Try to imagine it, Senpai.
The person you most love, cutting a
cake with a total stranger...
Cutting a cake...
Guahhh!!
Do you grasp it now, Senpai?
What an incorrigible fool I've been!
You can still make it right!
What's all this, now?
Thump
I just realized that I can't
do the cake-cutting scene!
Please, let me withdraw from the commercial!
Why can't you do the cake-cutting scene?
Nothing doing!
Kishimoto Weddings is a
very important sponsor!
I'm begging you!
Honestly!
All right, Fudo-kun.
Combined Weapon Proposal
Look at this.
The combined weapon made up
from your individual weapons
has been stalled for a while
due to lack of funding.
But just the other day, it became reality!
Thanks to their large contribution.
Although it's just a commercial, it's an
important part of our fight for world peace!
Please don't be unreasonable.
For the sake of world peace...
But is it worth making Desumi-san unhappy?
I made lots!
That's it!
What now?
I'll make my own cake
and do my first cake-cutting with Desumi
before the commercial is filmed!
No!
It's not good enough.
Fudo
You have no new messages
I ain't goin' in there!
Too dangerous.
What's all this about?
W-Well, you see...
Menacing
Is that...
Reaper-san?
He hasn't called me in two whole days!
Stupid, stupid, stupid Fudo!
All squad leaders and
Princess Series members,
report to the conference room at once.
Your attention, please!
The time is nigh!
This is the birth of our greatest
monster yet, the Ultimate Phantom!
For the sake of any viewers
who may have forgotten,
Allow me to explain!
allow me to explain once more!
Negative
Negative Energy
Secret Society Gekko is trying to use
the negative energy emitted by humans
Ultimate Phantom
to fuel the creation of the Ultimate
Phantom, their greatest monster yet!
Hey, about dang time!
It is your diligent efforts that
have made this day possible!
Behold! It's filled to the
brim with negative energy!
Now, let us celebrate!
Celebrate... Cake...
Cutting a cake...
At last, our plans for world
domination will bear fruit!
I feel you, Reaper Princess.
Our day is finally here!
Stupid Fudo...
Now, awaken!
Our greatest monster, Ultimate Phantom!
Ultimate
Pucka-pucka.
Goo-goo.
Pucka-pucka. Pucka.
It's not quite what I'd imagined.
Looks pretty weak to me.
Is it... a failure?
I-It can't be!
I created you for but one purpose!
Destroy humanity and bring
about our dream of—
Owie!
Wh-What in the world?!
Bosslar-sama!
What?!
Is it...
...out of control?
Why... Why?!
Ultimate Phantom!
Bad little boys who don't do as they're told
need punishment!
Major Yikes Kannonflame
Right here, kid!
Rampaging Lion Claws
Rampaging Lion Claws!
Bloody Slicer!
Bloody Slicer
Duàn Zuì Liè Lún!
Duàn Zuì Liè Lún
How d'you like that?
Step aside, Princess Series!
Fire!
Did we do it?!
What?!
It did nothing—
C-Culverin Bear-sama!
It ate him?!
Damn you!
It integrates whatever it eats?
N-Not good!
Desumi
Fudo
Radiance
All done!
Fudo-kun, it's time to head to the shoot!
Yes, sir!
Fudo-san!
Hashimoto-san!
Hey! What's with you, Reaper?
It ate Bear-sama!
Oh, for... Can someone
here get real already?!
It's heading for the city!
We have to go after it!
Please... pick up, Desumi-san!
Are you all right?
Ow, ow...
Yes, thanks. I'm fine.
Fudo
Hmph!
Sheesh, what a mess!
What a fool I've been.
Fudo-kun, I'd really like to start the shoot.
R-Right. Thanks.
Desumi-san
Calling
Desumi-san...
Is something the matter?
Not at all.
Really?
Then I hope we can get started!
Time for Scene 3, cutting the cake!
It's begun at last.
Action!
Excuse me, Fudo-san.
You're holding it too hard!
I'm sorry.
I can only cut my first cake with Desumi-san!
Pucka-pucka.
What is that monster?!
I'm currently over a wedding venue
where an explosion just occurred!
BREAKING
CITY WEDDING VENUE
SUDDEN EXPLOSION
Look at this!
The smoke hasn't even settled!
We can't tell if it's an accident
or intentional at this time.
But it's dangerous to be in the area,
so we implore everyone to stay away!
The explosion appears to be
the work of Ultimate Phantom.
I'm getting new information now.
It seems Fudo Aikawa of Gelato 5
was filming at this venue!
Fudo?
You need to get to safety!
I will!
Is this a new Gekko monster?
Destroy... humans.
Desumi
Fudo
The cake I made for Desumi-san and me!
Fudo!
You okay?
Did you really just turn
your back on the enemy?
Come on, let's get transformed!
Hey... were you crying?
C-Certainly not!
Let's go! Time to transform!
Freezing Change!
Five!
Four!
Three!
Two!
One!
Change Gelato!
The aroma of strawberry,
the flavor of justice!
Red Gelato!
The aroma of soda, the flavor of courage!
Blue Gelato!
The aroma of lemon, the flavor of life!
Yellow Gelato!
The aroma of peach, the flavor of love!
Pink Gelato!
The aroma of pistachio, the flavor of peace!
Green Gelato!
Together, we are...
Freezing Sentai Gelato 5!
Underestimate us on pain of fire!
Here's one for you!
Megaton Lemon Crush!
Misaki-san!
Let go of her!
Sky Peach Rain!
Right over here!
Twin Soda Slash!
Sweet Berry Impact!
Daigo-san!
Right!
Vacuum Pistachio Strike!
Your ferocity is truly admirable.
I only wish we could have
met under different—
Guys!
The building's coming down!
Are our heroes safe?!
Oh my!
L-Look at that!
The fight isn't over!
And the giant monster
seems completely unharmed!
I'm sorry, Fudo.
And it looks like our heroes
have taken quite a beating...
How in the world is this going to turn out?
Finally caught up.
It looks like Gekko reinforcements
have just arrived!
Not only are they facing a ferocious monster,
Here's our chance!
but the Princess Series
have also joined the fight!
Go, Gekko!
This might be the greatest
crisis Gelato 5 has ever faced!
You'll pay.
You'll pay!
Iron Prison!
Iron Prison
Oh! There seems to be some
in-fighting going on!
What could be the cause of it?!
I'll slice you to ribbons!
S-Steel!
Y-You damned monster...
It appears Gekko doesn't have
control of this monster.
And now...
It's devouring the cake!
It just does whatever it wants!
This thing...
The monster's appearance is changing!
Fudo...
Desumi
Fudo
That thing is incredible!
Red here.
Fudo-kun, hold it horizontal!
Fudo-kun.
We're left with no other choice.
It'll be quite a test run, but you'll
have to use that weapon we discussed.
The Combiner Sword, Gelato Claymore!
That weapon will surely defeat the monster.
Everyone, combine your weapons!
Let's go!
Combine!
Complete! Gelato Claymore!
Are you seeing this, everyone?
Gelato 5's weapons, and their hearts...
are united!
Everyone!
Blue, Green, Pink, and
Yellow have been captured!
Red's wound appears quite serious.
What in the world will happen next?!
Damn it!
What is this?!
It can't be!
Reaper Princess joins the battle!
I can't believe what I'm seeing!
Those two eternal rivals...
working as a team?!
Desumi-san?
I'm sorry for being selfish.
I'm sure you must hate me now.
I wouldn't. Never ever.
Not even if the heavens fell to the earth!
Fudo!
Desumi-san.
I can't hear what they're saying,
but it's easy to imagine it's
a heated exchange of insults!
Are you ready, Fudo?
I am, Desumi-san!
I know they can do this!
Just do it, Reaper!
Go!
What? Fudo, is this...
Yes, this is...
...like we're cutting a cake!
Heck yeah!
Running away with the glory...
They did it!
That's my Fudo!
Big Sister!
Big Sis!
Thank you, Desumi-san.
I would have lost for sure if not for you.
I'm the one who should thank you.
You made us a cake, didn't you?
I'd love to actually eat the next one!
Easily provided, Desumi-san!
This child... isn't it that monster?
I think it is.
It's too small to cause any
more harm now, I'm sure.
Papa! Mama!
R-Really!
This appears to be a case
of mistaken identity!
Honestly, what a silly baby!
After vanquishing the giant monster,
has a new friendship sprung up between them?!
Let's have an interview!
Rondo of the Reaper!
Reaper Rondo
Th-There's no mutual understanding at all!
N-Not bad, Reaper Princess!
F-Friendship? Don't be absurd!
I am Reaper Princess.
The cold and merciless devil incarnate!
Never forget that.
Mama! Mama!
Let us meet again, De—
Reaper Princess!
A-Any time, Fu—
Red Gelato!
Allow me to explain!
This is the story of a hero of justice
and a secret society's combatant
walking the road of forbidden love!